Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Faculty Publications, 1844-1994 RG.1.1
New York University Archives
- Faculty Publications
  - Stevenson, J.J., Report on Geology of Colorado in 1873, 1874 (Box 28, Item 1)
  - Sihler, E.G., Annals of Caesar: A Critical Biography with a Survey of the Sources, 1911 (Box 28, Item 2)
  - Sinding, Paul C., History of Scandinavia, 1866 (Box 28, Item 3)
  - Nason, Arthur Huntington, James Shirley Dramatist, 1915 (Box 28, Item 4)
  - Sihler, E.G., Cicero of Arpinum, 1914 (Box 28, Item 5)
  - Zurcher, Arnold J., Constitutions and Constitutional Trends since World War II, 1951 (Box 28, Item 6)
  - Reid, James D., The Telegraph in America, 1879 (Box 28, Item 7)
  - Stevenson, J.J., Varia 2 (Various Publications), 1872-1909 (Box 28, Item 8)
  - Meredith, Albert B., Madden, John T., MacCracken, John H., Bouton, Archibald L., Obligations of Universities (Various "Addresses and Discussion"), 1933 (Box 28, Item 9)
  - Morse, Edward Lind, Samuel F.B. Morse, Letters and Journals, 1914 (Box 28, Item 10)
  - Millican, Charles Bowie, Spenser and the Table Round, 1932 (Box 28, Item 11)
  - Stahl, William Harris, Macrobius, Commentary on the Dream of Scipio, 1952 (Box 28, Item 12)
  - Hahn, A., Alexander Meyrowitz; Key to the Massoretic Notes, Titles, and Index Generally Found in the Margin of the Hebrew Bible, 1889 (Box 30)
  - Jones, Theodore Francis, "New York University, 1932-1932", 1933 (Box 31)
  - Potash, David M., "The Graduate School of Arts and Science at New York University", 1991 (Box 31)